译者：微博@Emtee
爱之女巫
译者:微博@Emtee
我在开启一段新的生活
I'm starting a new life.
这里红杉林立  静谧又干净
Up here where it's quiet and clean among the redwoods.
几乎没人认识我
And almost no one knows me.
可怜的杰瑞
Poor Jerry.
他离开我之后 我精神失常了
I had a nervous breakdown after he left me.
他们说 现在我已痊愈
They say I'm cured now.
但我仍有侵入性想法
But I still have intrusive thoughts.
我的治疗师告诉我 像我这样的不在少数
My therapist told me that I'm not unusual at all.
他们遍布世界各地
People are abused all over the world
每天都受凌虐
every day
比我更严重
much worse than me
而他们都挺好
and they do fine.
小姐 你的尾灯坏了
Your tail light's out, miss.
谢谢提醒
Thank you for letting me know.
你要给我开罚单吗
Are you gonna write me a ticket?
这次就算了 但务必修好它
I'll let ya go this time, but make sure you get it fixed.
谢谢 警官
Thank you, officer.
开车注意安全
You drive safely.
杰瑞一离开我 我就倾我所能
When Jerry left me, I devoured everything
了解了关于如何俘获男人的方法
I could about how to get your man back.
据专家所说 男人都很弱
According to the experts, men are very fragile.
只要你会表现自己 他们就会被迷倒
They can get crushed down if you assert yourself in any way.
你得工于心计
You have to be very tricky.
伊莲?
Elaine?
嗨 我是雀茜
Hi, I'm Trish.
嗨 雀茜 很高兴见到你
Hi, Trish, it's nice to meet you.
你真漂亮
You're so pretty.
我没别的意思
Oh, um, I didn't mean anything.
我已经结婚了
I'm married and everything.
我没多想
No, I didn't think anything.
我来帮你拎包吧
Well, let me help you with your bags.
就这些吗
Is this all you've got?
暂时是的
For now.
我的艺术用品之后会被运来
My art supplies are being shipped over later.
你是个艺术家?
So you're an artist?
是的
Yes, I am.
我是个室内装修师
I'm an interior decorator.
真的?
Oh, really?
没错
Yes.
我和芭芭拉就是因为装修认识的 我装修了这套公寓
That's how I met Barbara.I decorated this apartment.
幸好我还留着钥匙
It was lucky I still had the keys.
芭芭拉完全不清楚自己什么时候会回来
Barbara didn't exactly know when she'd be back.
你怎么认识芭芭拉的
How do you know Barbara?
在旧金山时 我们常一起跳舞
We used to dance together in San Francisco.
是吗
Really?
但愿你喜欢这套公寓
Well, I hope you like the apartment.
有点俗艳 但芭芭拉想这样
It's a bit garish but Barbara wanted it that way.
她让我用上托特塔罗牌里的所有颜色
She had me take all of the colors from the Thoth tarot deck
她和她的学生们还画了一堆玄妙的画让我挂
and she and her students did a bunch of occult paintings for me to hang.
她喜欢一切巫术类的东西
She's into all that Wicca stuff.
就是这里
Well, this is it.
雀茜 我很喜欢
Oh, Trish, I love it.
好美
It's just beautiful.
真的吗
Really?
很高兴你这么说
Oh, I'm so glad.
我还以为太过俗艳了
I thought I may have overdone it.
没有 我就喜欢这样的
Oh no, it's exactly my taste.
你一定累坏了 想必你想躺下休息了吧
You must be exhausted.I'm sure you want to lie down.
实际上 我想吃点东西
Actually, I was thinking about getting a bite to eat.
这附近你了解吗
Do you know of a place around here?
有家维多利亚式茶馆
There's the Victorian tea room.
我们能一起去 你不介意有伴的话
We could go together, if you don't mind the company.
那太好了
Oh, how fantastic.
我能在哪梳洗
Where can I freshen up?
卧室在那边
The bedroom is through there.
马上就好
I'll only be a moment.
这地方好漂亮
What a lovely room.
当然啦
Yes, isn't it?
我喜欢维多利亚式的东西
I love Victoriana.
在这里就像成了童话里的公主
Being here is like being a Princess in a fairy tale.
伊莲 你有公主梦吗
Do you have fairy Princess fantasies, Elaine?
当然
Of course.
我们已是成年女性 但心里面
We may be grown women, but underneath
我们只是梦想着被白马王子
we're just little girls dreaming about being carried off
带走的小女孩
by a prince on a white horse.
或许吧
Yes, I suppose so.
挺荒谬的 不是吗
It's ridiculous, isn't it?
我想我还没找到我的白马王子
I don't think I've found my prince charming yet,
但我想我找到了方法
but I think I found the formula.
我一直在研究超心理学
You know, I've been studying parapsychology
我对男人的了解比过去多得多了
and I understand men so much better than I used to.
我以前就那么了解的话
If only I would have known before what I know now.
杰瑞就不会永远离开我了
Then Jerry would have never left me.
杰瑞是谁
Who's Jerry?
我的前夫
My exhusband.
他离开我的那天就是我死去的日子
The day he left me was the day that I died.
但之后 我重生为女巫了
But then I was reborn as a witch.
芭芭拉和加恩让我重生了
Barbara and Gahan brought me back to life.
他们教了我关于魔法和男人的一切
They taught me everything I know about magic and about men.
男人就像孩子一样
Men are like children.
他们很容易被讨好
They're very easy to please
只要我们给他们想要的
as long as we give them what they want.
我们刚说到哪了
Where were we?
对了 男人 你说我们得给他们想要的
Oh, men, you said we need to give them what they want.
男人想要什么呢
Well, what do men want?
只想要个漂亮女人来爱 但也要能照顾他们
Just a pretty woman to love and to take care of them
能让他们感觉自己是男人
and to make them feel like a man
能在任何方面给予他们完全的自由
and to give them total freedom in whatever they wanna do or be.
可我们想要的呢
But what about what we want?
如果我们一直满足他们的需求
How are we going to be equals with men
那怎么才能男女平等呢
if we keep catering to all of their needs?
我认为如果你想要爱情 那你就得给予爱情
I think that if you want love, you have to give love.
给予男人性爱是释放他们潜在感情的一种方式
Giving men sex is a way of unlocking their love potential.
你讲得就像你被男权制社会洗脑了似的
You sound as if you'd been brainwashed by the patriarchy.
你的整个自我价值就在于取悦男人
Your whole selfworth is wrapped up in pleasing a man.
我承认我用性爱得到这东西
I'll admit, I used sex to get this,
但我并不为此感到骄傲
but I'm not proud of it.
全世界不是围绕着一个男人的需求转的
A whole world doesn't revolve around a man's needs.
如果每次理查德想做爱了 我就和他做
If I gave Richard sex every time he wanted it,
那我早残废了
I'd be a wreck.
可怜的理查
Poor Richard.
他爱你 也想要你 你却折磨他
He loves you and he wants you and you torture him.
你必须满足男人的幻想
You have to give a man his fantasy.
男人的幻想?
His fantasy?
没错 男人的幻想
Yes, his fantasy.
但我真正感兴趣的
But what I'm really interested in
是爱情
is love.
你也许会说我痴迷于爱情
You might say I'm addicted to love.
我好奇是不是所有女人都那么想
I wonder if all women feel that way?
那要看你说的爱情是什么意思
Well, it depends on what you mean by love.
丈夫不是王子 伊莲
A husband isn't a prince, Elaine,
生活也不是童话
and life isn't a fairy tale.
我们必须面对这个事实
We have to face that fact.
为什么
Why?
或许你多取悦取悦你丈夫
Maybe life could be a fairy tale
生活就会是童话了
if you pleased your husband more.
我不需要取悦理查德
I don't need to please Richard.
理查德是因为我这个人而爱我
Richard loves me for myself.
当然
Of course.
可能你确实是找到了你的白马王子
Maybe you did find your prince charming.
可能确实如此
Perhaps I did.
猜猜是谁
Guess who.
理查德 你怎么在这
Richard, what are you doing here?
这个茶馆仅限女性
This tea room is for ladies only.
我在上班时间去找你了 朱莉说你在这里
Oh, I went to visit you at work and Julie said you were here.
我本想我们一起吃午餐
I thought we could have lunch together.
很贴心 但我已经吃过午餐了
Well, that's very sweet, but I've already had my lunch.
对了 理查德 这是伊莲
Oh, uh, Richard, this is Elaine.
伊莲 这是我的丈夫 理查德
Elaine, this is my husband, Richard.
我听过很多关于你的事 理查德
I've heard so much about you, Richard.
但愿没有太糟的
Nothing too horrible, I hope.
正相反
On the contrary.
法术书
爱情法术
女神 求你了
Goddess, please,
给我一个英俊 温柔的男人
send me a beautiful, sweet man
要和我爱他一样爱我
to love me as I love him.
要爱我 爱我
To love me, love me,
爱我
love me,
love me.
月升草药
魔法药店
嗨 你是温迪吗
Hi, are you Wendy?
是的 我能为你做什么
Yes, what can I do for you?
我是伊莲
I'm Elaine.
我们通过电话 我是制作手工皂和蜡烛的
We spoke on the phone.I make natural soaps and candles and things.
伊莲啊 想起来了
Elaine, right.
谢谢来访
Thanks for coming by.
我能看下吗
Mind if I have a look?
看吧
Please do.
这些都不错
These are nice.
爱情魔法
非常不错
Really nice.
我觉得这些会卖得不错
I think these will do well in the store.
那你是要了吗
Then you'll take them?
先卖这些 看看情况
Let's start with these and see how they do.
爱情魔法
伊莲制造
下周或下下周都卖掉的话 我会订更多的
If these sell in the next week or two, I'll order more.
怎么样
Sound good?
太好了
Yes, fantastic.
谢谢 温迪
Thank you, Wendy.
不客气 伊莲
Sure, Elaine.
祝福你
Bright blessings.
人们总问我 为什么我是个女巫
People always ask me why I'm a witch.
我告诉他们 那是因为我想拥有魔力
I tell them it's because I wanna have magical powers.
但它不是听上去那么回事
But it's not like it sounds.
它仅仅是用你的意志去得到你想要的
All it is is using your will to get what you want.
嗨
Hi.
今天天气真好
It's a beautiful day.
是啊
Yes, it is.
我喜欢在这样的日子里体验大自然
I love to be out in nature on days like this.
你喜欢大自然?
Oh, you like nature?
非常喜欢
Very much.
你看上去也是个喜欢大自然的人
You seem like a nature type too.
我敢打赌你喜欢在树林里消磨时间
I'll bet you like to spend time in the woods.
没错
That's right.
你怎么知道
How'd you know?
我能看出来
I can just tell.
大自然是你的心之所在
Nature is where your heart is.
城市和人让你感到厌烦
City and people can get to be too much for you.
几秒钟就从一个人身上看出这么多了啊
Whuh, that is a lot to get from someone in a few seconds.
我在这方面很有天赋
I'm talented that way.
我对城市的看法 你说得没错
Well, you're right about the city.
实际上 我在树林里有栋房子 离这里约一个小时的路程
In fact, I have a house out in the woods about an hour from here.
我有时间了 就喜欢去那里
I like to go there whenever I can to, you know,
思考 阅读
just think and read.
你带你妻子去那里吗
Do you take your wife up there?
不带
No.
我没结婚
I'm not married.
那你至少会偶尔带个姑娘去那里
Well, you might at least take a girl up there once in a while.
没错
I do.
没错 偶尔
I do, once in a while.
你想现在带个姑娘过去吗
You wanna take a girl up there now?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我刚来这里
Well, I'm new in town
还没怎么体验过周围的大自然
and I haven't seen much of the nature around here.
我会给你做一顿好吃的晚餐
I'll make you a nice dinner.
好的 没问题
Yes, yes, okay, sure.
我的车就在那边
Uh, my car is right over there.
好的
Okay.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你知道我现在想做什么吗
You know what I'd like to do right now?
我想像小孩那样在车里做爱
I'd like to make love right here in the car just like we were kids.
等等 等等
Wait, wait.
想喝点吗
You want some?
这是什么
What is it?
是我做的
Something I made.
好烈啊
That is, that is strong.
把它喝完
Finish it.
韦恩 韦恩 别这样
No, Wayne, Wayne, stop.
别在这里
Not here.
我们进去吧
Let's go inside.
好漂亮
This is beautiful.
我去做晚餐
I'll start the dinner.
看上去很美味
This looks delicious.
敬大自然
To nature.
这样很棒 对吧
This is really nice, isn't it?
我常在学期末来这里放松
I like to come up here a lot at the end of the semester to unwind.
你是位老师吗
Are you a teacher?
是啊 我在大学教书
Yeah, I teach at the university.
教什么的
What do you teach?
英国和法国文学
English and French literature
主要是18世纪的
with a focus on the 18th century.
所以 你一定是个很放荡的人
So, you must be quite a libertine.
放荡的人?
A libertine?
你为什么会那么说
Why would you say that?
你知道的
Oh, you know.
所有危险的暧昧关系都是班尼·希尔风格的
All of the dangerous liaisons, Benny hill stuff.
更别说卡萨诺瓦了
Not to mention Casanova.
18世纪的书多着呢
Well, there were a lot of books written in the 18th century.
是真的吗
Well, is it true?
你是个放荡的人吗
Are you a libertine?
是的
Yes I am.
我喜欢女人
I love women.
你介意吗
Does that bother you?
正相反
On the contrary.
我觉得怪怪的 头好晕
I feel strange, dizzy.
你给我喝的东西里有什么
What was in that drink you gave me?
有机浆果 伏特加 致幻草药
Organic berries, vodka, hallucinogenic herbs.
致幻草药?
Hallucinogenic herbs?
宝贝啊
Oh, baby.
你真的很疯狂
You are really wild.
你介意我让自己更舒服些吗
Would you mind if I made myself more comfortable?
完全不介意
Not at all.
什么情况
What the hell?
你的外套
Your coat.
太亮了
It's so bright.
我总会裱褙我的衣物
I always line my clothing.
你有两个自我
You have two selves.
你向世界所展现的黑暗与安静
Dark and quiet that you show the world.
你要把那个给谁
Who do you give that to?
彩虹?
The rainbow?
我要把彩虹给你
I give the rainbow to you.
马上就给
Right now.
天啊
Oh god.
伊莲
Oh, Elaine.
看看你啊
Look at you.
现在你能和我做爱了
You can make love to me now.
好了
Okay.
怎么了 韦恩
What is it, Wayne?
怎么了 宝贝
What is it, baby?
伊莲 我感觉好怪
Oh, Elaine, I feel so strange.
没事的 有我在呢
It's all right, you're with me.
伊莲
Elaine.
以前从没女人那样委身于我
No woman has ever given herself like that to me before.
人生坎坷 对吧
Life has been tough, huh?
某方面来说 是的
Yeah, in a way.
你和我遇见的其他女人不一样
You're not like any other woman I've met.
不耍手段 没有企图
No games, no agendas.
你似乎就是顺应人生
You just seem to take life as it is.
还有其他方式对待人生吗
Is there any other way to take life?
我相处过的女人
Well, the women I've been with,
你一和她们上床 她们就要你对她们做出一堆承诺
they all want you to make a bunch of promises to 'em as soon as you sleep with 'em.
但你怎么能向自己都不认识的人做出承诺呢
But, how can you commit to someone that you don't even know?
这太疯狂了
It's crazy.
我懂 宝贝
I know, baby.
我懂
I know.
我从没想到自己会心有所属
I never thought I wanted to be tied down to anybody.
但那只是因为以前从没遇到完全对的人
But it's just 'cause no one was ever quite right.
那些身体让我着迷的女人
All the women that I'm attracted to physically
都不够聪慧
they're never bright enough.
而那些聪慧的都相貌平平 不会让我有欲望
And all the bright ones are homely and don't arouse me.
这似乎是个大问题
That seems like quite a problem.
没错
It is.
我觉得我一生都是个独行者
I feel my whole life as a loner,
认为自己不需要任何人
thinkin' I didn't need anybody.
但现在我不那么确定了
But now I'm not so sure.
伊莲
Oh, Elaine,
我以前从没感受过真正的爱情
I have never felt real love like this before.
你现在太多愁善感了
You're just having a lot of emotions right now.
伊莲 我好害怕
Elaine, I'm scared.
我不习惯这种强烈的感觉
I'm not used to feeling things so strongly.
我承受不住 我承受不住
I can't take it, I can't take it.
伊莲 我病了
Elaine, I'm sick.
我病了
I'm sick.
嘿 没事的
Hey, it's all right.
有我在呢
I've got you.
我爱你
I love you.
我永远都会在你身边
And I'll always be here for you.
睡会儿吧
Try to get some sleep.
伊莲
Elaine.
伊莲 你在哪
Elaine, where are you?
真是个娘们儿
What a pussy.
真是个孩子
What a baby.
我还以为我找到了一个真正的男人
I thought I'd found a real man,
但他就像个小女孩
but he's just like a little girl.
伊莲！
Elaine!
我哭得撕心裂肺时 可从没有人在我身边
No one was ever there for me when I was crying my heart out.
从没有人安慰过我
No one ever comforted me.
没有人
No one.
早上好 韦恩
Good morning, Wayne.
嗨 伊莲
Hi, Elaine.
给 喝吧
Here, drink this.
昨晚我做了个很可怕的梦
I had such horrible dreams last night.
梦到了什么 宝贝
What did you dream about, baby.
梦到自己在呼喊你的名字
I dreamt that I was calling your name
而你却毫无回应
and you didn't answer.
我不停地呼喊 但我却找不到你
I kept calling and calling, but I couldn't find you.
伊莲 你爱我的 对吗
Oh, Elaine, you love me, don't you?
我当然爱你
Of course, I love you.
天呐 伊莲
Oh god, oh god, Elaine.
你饿吗
Are you hungry?
我不知道我怎么了
I don't know what I am.
睡会儿吧
Well, try to get some sleep.
伊莲
Elaine.
别离开我
Don't leave me.
我哪都不去 宝贝
I'm not going anywhere, baby.
我马上回来
I'll be right here.
韦恩 醒醒
Wayne, wake up.
不早了
It's late.
韦恩
Wayne.
韦恩 宝贝 醒醒
Wayne, baby, wake up.
醒醒
Wake up.
韦恩
Wayne.
卫生棉条并不恶心
Tampons aren't gross.
女人会月经 而经血是一样美丽的东西
Women bleed and that's a beautiful thing.
你知道 很多男人都没见过一根被用过的卫生棉条吗
Do you know that most men have ever even seen a used tampon?
部分的我现在可以和韦恩在一起了
Part of me can be with Wayne now.
永远地
Always.
我真不介意死亡
I don't really mind death.
我以前埋过人
I've buried people before.
是我真正在乎的人
People I really cared about.
不管怎样 我们最终都会变成肥料
In the end we're all just compost anyway.
一切都会重生
Everything regenerates.
我想重生为一只猫
I'd like to come back as a cat.
我的猫死后 我一直很沮丧
I've been so depressed since my cat died.
他叫格雷马尔金 是黑白色的 他是我最好的朋友
His name was Greymalkin, but he was black and white.He was my best friend.
我要把彩虹给你
I give the rainbow to you.
马上给你
Right now.
稍等
Just a minute.
嗨 雀茜
Oh hi Trish.
进来吧
Come on in.
嘿 伊莲
Hey, Elaine.
你看起来美极了
You look gorgeous.
我喜欢你的发型
I love what you've done with your hair.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 有事吗 亲爱的 - 我一直没能联系到你
- What's up, honey? - Well, I haven't been able to reach you,
所以我想我过来看看一切是否安好
so I thought I'd come over to see if everything was all right.
我很好
I'm fine.
真的
Really.
你要吃点或喝点什么吗
Can I offer you something?
我刚沏了茶 做了蛋糕
I just made some tea and cake.
茶就行了 谢谢
Just tea, thank you.
要加奶油和糖吗
Cream and sugar?
不用 谢了
No, I'm fine, thank you.
你一直都在忙什么
So, what have you been so busy with?
但愿是男人的事
A man, I hope.
没错 是男人的事
Yes, it was a man.
但没成
But, it didn't work out.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
真是可惜 我很喜欢他
Yes, it's a shame and I really liked him.
以为就是他了
I thought that he was the one.
也许下次能找到
Well, maybe next time.
你确定不要吃蛋糕吗
Are you sure you won't have some cake?
不了 谢谢
Oh, no, thank you.
我只是过来看下你 并跟你道别的
I just came over to check up on you and to say good bye.
道别?
Good bye?
为什么 你要去哪
Why, where are you going?
只是去达拉斯参加一个家具业大会
Oh, just to Dallas for a furniture convention.
理查德也去吗
Is Richard going with you?
不去 我出差而已
No, it's just a business trip.
理查德得照顾自己一阵子了
Richard will have to fend for himself for a while.
山姆 给我两杯加冰威士忌
Sam, give me two whiskeys on the rocks.
没问题 简
Sure thing, Jane.
你看了今天的报纸没
You see the papers today?
没 怎么了
No, why?
有具尸体在鳗鱼河里被发现了
They found a body in the eel river.
谋杀?
A murder?
或许吧
Maybe.
他的胸口上被刻了一个标志
They found a symbol carved in his chest.
看
Here.
是颗五芒星
It's a pentagram.
又跟巫师有关
It's them witches again.
我也是这么想的 莱尔
That's what I was thinking too, Lyle.
芭芭拉 就是这样
So yeah, Barbara, that's everything.
杰瑞死后 警察不停地烦扰我
After Jerry died, the cops wouldn't stop harassing me.
他们什么都证明不了
They couldn't prove anything.
却认为是我杀了他
They actually thought that I killed him.
你敢信?
Can you believe it?
总之 你走之后 旧金山之行变得很不愉快
Anyways, San Francisco got to be a really bad trip after you left.
我就是在那时想起你还有套公寓
That's when I remembered you had that extra apartment.
这时间真是完美
Well, it was perfect timing.
我只是很抱歉没能在场欢迎你
I'm just sorry I wasn't here to greet you.
没什么的
That's all right.
雀茜很友好
Trish has been lovely.
我做了很多艺术品
And I've been getting a lot of artwork done.
上周有件事真的震惊到我了
But I had this experience last weekend that really shook me up.
怎么了 发生了什么事
Why, what happened?
我遇见了一个很帅的男人
Well, I met this greatlooking guy.
我对他用了爱情魔法
And I used love magic on him.
之后他对我变得很怪
Then he got really weird on me.
他所有的情感都开始流露了出来
All these emotions started flowing out of him.
然后他就真的
Then he got really
病了
sick.
男人不太会控制自己的情感
Well, guys can't handle their emotions too well.
所以他们不喜欢沉重的谈话
That's why they don't like heavy conversations.
他大概就是承受不住
It was probably just too much for him.
你给他的爱情与美妙性爱
All the love and the great sex that you were giving him.
我想就是这么回事吧
I guess that's what it was.
但我说不清
But, I don't know.
亲爱的 你得多加小心
Honey, you have to be more careful.
或许你起初就不该乱用爱情法术
Maybe you shouldn't be messing with love spells in the first place, you know.
很高兴见到你 伊莲
Merry meet, Elaine.
祝福你 加恩
Bright blessings Gahan.
我听到你们在讨论爱情法术
I heard you discussing love spells.
伊莲 你务必小心
You do have to be careful, Elaine.
爱情法术从不会像你想的那样奏效
Love spells never work the way you think they will.
但值得一提的是 见到你真是太好了 伊莲
But on a lighter note, it's wonderful to see you, Elaine.
多久没见了 一年?
What's it been now, a year?
我们必须庆祝下好友重聚
We must celebrate this reunion of dear friends.
感谢无处不在的女神
Thank you goddess everywhere
所赐予我们的祝福
for the blessings that we share.
瓦丽亚 应当被称颂
Blessed be, Variah.
回家去 巫师们
Go home, witches.
回家吧
Go home.
无视他们就好
Just ignore them.
他们总给我们制造麻烦
They're always giving us trouble.
我不知道这地方对巫师有敌意
I didn't know this town was hostile to witches.
这里又不是旧金山
Well, it's certainly not San Francisco.
但对于一个小镇而言 这里算不错了
But it's not bad for a small town.
不是所有人都能接受我们实施巫术的方式
Not all of them embrace our methods of practicing witchcraft.
但我不明白现在我们为什么要那么紧张
But, I don't see why we ought to be so uptight now.
想当年 我们都自由地做爱
Back in the day, we all made love freely
张贴巴弗灭海报 没人会教条地看他们
and put up Baphomet posters and no one was dogmatic
是否是巫师 或撒旦信徒 或泰勒玛信徒
about whether they were a witch or a satanist or thelemites,
或德鲁伊 或威卡信徒 或别的什么
or a druid or a wiccan or whatever.
而那很有趣
And it was fun.
但我们的课程和魔法圈一直很受喜爱
But our classes and circles have been very popular.
你们都教什么
What have you been teaching?
我想想 我带了个新班 教的西卓尔魔法
Let's see, I've got a new class on Sidral magic
芭芭拉也带了个新班 教的是奥根炼金术
and Barbara's got a new class on organite alchemy.
此外 我们还教主要课程
Otherwise, we're still teaching the staples,
能量基础 地基灵修
energy grounding, earthbased spirituality,
异教徒手工艺
pagan arts and crafts,
蜡烛制作 大师级法术工艺 古代神秘学
candle work, the spellcraft master class, ancient mysticism,
草药和香料 当然还有性爱魔法
herbs and spices, and sex magic, of course.
你还教性爱魔法吗
Are you still teaching that?
教啊 实际上 今晚我们为情欲舞蹈的力量这堂课
Yes, in fact, we've invited some girls here tonight
请了些姑娘过来
for a seminar about the power of sexual dancing.
舞蹈是女人和女孩的强大力量
Dancing is such a powerful thing for women and girls.
你还跳舞吗
Are you still dancing?
跳啊 我们有些人会在业余者之夜跳
Yeah, some of us dance here on amateur night.
你也来吧
You should come.
嗨 芭芭拉
Hi, Barbara.
嗨 加恩
Hi, Gahan.
对不起 我们来晚了
Sorry we're late.
你们好 可爱的两位女士 请坐吧
Hello lovely ladies, please have a seat.
伊莲 这两姐妹分别是星星和月亮
Elaine, this is star and her sister moon.
她们是我们今晚的学生
They're our students for tonight.
姑娘们 这位是我们的好朋友 伊莲
Girls, this is our dear friend Elaine.
嗨
Hi.
我刚提到舞蹈是女人和女孩的强大力量
I was just pointing out that dancing is a powerful thing for women and girls.
叫你们今晚来见我们
We asked you to meet us here tonight
就是要你们学习学习
so you could learn about that.
你们看到那女孩的力量有多强大吗
Do you see how powerful that girl is?
这些男人会为她做任何事
These men would do anything for her.
你们很想自己拥有那种力量吧
Wouldn't you like to have that power yourselves?
那我们开始吧
Then let us begin.
所有女巫都得搞清楚她们的力量在哪
All witches need to figure out where their power lies.
我们觉得一个女人最强大的力量在于她的性
And we feel that a woman's greatest power lies in her sexuality.
我们认为这种力量并非罪恶 也非反女性主义
We don't view this power as satanic or antifeminist,
而是女性作为自然生物的一种礼赞
but as a celebration of woman as a natural creature.
是一个尘世之躯 一种精神实质 一处孕育之所
An earthly body, a spiritual essence, and a womb.
整个巫术历史都与害怕女性的性相交织
The whole history of witchcraft is interwoven with the fear of female sexuality.
我们被绑在火刑柱上烧死
They burned us at the stake
是因为人们害怕被我们以非正当手段所勾起的情欲
because they feared the erotic feelings we illicited in them.
后来 人们用婚姻使我们被束缚
Later, they used marriage to hold us in bondage
我们被迫成了女仆 妓女和性爱娃娃
and made us into servants, whores, and fantasy dolls
而我们想要什么却无人问津
never asking us what we wanted.
他们告诉我们 超理性主义且恬淡寡欲的男人是人的标准
They teach us that a normative human being is a hyperrationalist, stoic male
而女人的情感和直觉是需要被治疗的病患
and that women's emotions and intuitions are illnesses that need to be cured.
他们认为男人和女人是不同的
And they believe that men and women are different
真正的平等就在于这种不同
and that true equality lies in that difference.
我们谋求男女极性
We strive for male/female polarity
并以女神之身重获我们的原始力量
and to regain our primal power as goddesses.
我们得用男人能理解的方式
We need to teach men how to love us
教他们怎么爱我们
using ways they can understand.
所以女神们 使用香水
So goddesses, use perfume,
穿高跟鞋 化妆
wear high heels and makeup,
学会打造吸引人的发型
learn to dress your hair in attractive ways,
巧妙地展现肉体 并知道该隐藏什么
display flesh artfully, and know what to conceal.
做一个母亲和一个情人
Be a mother and a lover.
坚定自己的立场 但永远都要让男人感觉自己是男人
Stand your ground, but always let the man feel like a man.
用性爱魔法摧毁他对你的恐惧
Use sex magic to destroy his fear of you
将他的心向爱情闸门敞开
and to open his heart to the floodgates of love.
只有那时 他才会开始把你看作是一个人 看到你所有的内在美
Only then will he begin to see you as a human being with all of your inner beauty.
他对爱情敞开心扉之后
Then, when his heart is open to love,
你想和他做什么都可以
you may do with him what you will.
我爱你 伊莲
I love you, Elaine.
你知道的 对吗
You know that, don't you?
我非常爱你
I love you very much.
但你得多加注意
But you need to be more careful.
这周晚餐晚了三次
Dinner was late three times this week.
家里完全是个猪圈
And that house is a total pigsty.
你知道今早我在床下发现了一条很久前的热狗吗
Do you know that I found an old hot dog under the bed this morning?
你为什么从不梳头
And why don't you ever brush your hair?
你得好好照顾自己和这个家
You need to take better care of yourself and of the house.
我都不好意思请人来做客
I'm embarrassed to have people over.
之前 我一直很有耐心
I've been really patient up until now,
女巫飞行软膏
但你得快点进入状态
but you need to step up your game.
你真是个疯婊子
I have a crazy bitch for a daughter.
什么
What?
你没疯
You're not crazy.
你没疯的话 那你就是傻
Well, if you're not crazy then you're stupid.
是哪个呢
Which is it?
你是疯还是傻
Are you crazy or are you stupid?
你可以瘦掉几磅的
And you could lose a few pounds.
你看上去有点胖
You're looking a little fatty.
天呐 伊莲 你瘦了好多
Oh my god, Elaine, you've lost so much weight.
你现在的身材太棒了
You have such a hot body now.
你喜欢我这样摸
Do you like it when I touch you like this?
还是这样摸
Or like this?
我想让你高潮
I wanna make you come.
别害怕 伊莲
Don't be frightened, Elaine.
我绝不会伤害你
I would never hurt you.
我不是大坏狼
I'm not the big, bad wolf.
你得有绝对的爱和绝对的信任
You need to have perfect love and perfect trust.
你有勇气尝试吗
Hast thou the courage to make the assay?
我有两样东西 绝对的爱和绝对的信任
I have two words, perfect love and perfect trust.
协助我建好
Assist me to erect the ancient altar
在过去做礼拜仪式的古代祭坛
at which in days past all worshiped.
在旧时代 女人就是祭坛
From the old times, a woman was the altar.
圣地是魔法圈中心内的点
And the sacred place was the point within the center of the circle,
即万物的起源
the origin of all things.
因此 我们应该崇拜它
Therefore, should we adore it.
早上好 格里夫警长
Good morning, sergeant Griff.
恭喜升官
Congratulations on your promotion.
谢谢 康妮
Thanks, Connie.
有咖啡吗
Is there any coffe?
有啊 我刚做了些
Yeah, I just made some.
按你喜欢的口味做的
I made it just the way you like it.
有什么事是你做不好的吗
Is there anything you don't do well?
有机会就试试我 自己去发现咯
Why don't you try me sometime and find out?
咖啡怎么样 史蒂夫
How's the coffee, Steve?
太浓了
Uh, too strong.
我喜欢浓的
Well, I like it strong.
男人毕竟要在工作中保持清醒
Man's gotta stay awake on the job after all.
为什么 你一直要忙到深夜吗
Why, have you been keeping late nights?
或许吧
Maybe so.
可你现在已经升官了
But, now that you've been promoted,
或许你该开始考虑安顿下来了
maybe you ought to start thinking about settling down.
我? 你开玩笑吧
Me, you kidding?
梅多斯警长 一位女士有事找你
Sergeant Meadows, a lady's here to see you.
我是雪莉·柯蒂斯
I'm Shelly Curtis.
我打电话说过韦恩·彼得斯的事 失踪的那个教师
I phoned about Wayne Peters, the teacher who disappeared.
是的
Yes, of course.
坐吧 柯蒂斯小姐
Have a seat, miss Curtis.
你说你觉得彼得斯先生可能被绑架了?
You say you think Mr. Peters might have been kidnapped?
没错 他有两周没被人看到了
Yes, no one's seen him for two weeks.
我去了他家 邮件都成堆了
I went by his house and the mail's piled up.
他失踪的那天 我们一起吃过午餐
We had lunch the day he disappeared.
我看见他在广场旁边和一个陌生女人开车走了
I saw him drive away with a strange woman near the Plaza.
你知道他和她会去哪吗
Do you have any idea where he might have gone with her?
韦恩过周末会去他的林中小屋
Wayne used to spend weekends up in a cabin he had in the woods.
他常在那约会
He used to take dates there.
天呐
Jesus.
嘿 格里夫 看啊
Hey Griff, look.
我的天
Good lord.
这到底是什么
What the hell is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们得挖开 史蒂夫
We're going to have to dig, Steve.
我知道
I know.
我想你该回屋里 雪莉
I think you should go back to the house, Shelly.
这蛋糕太美味了
This cake is absolutely fantastic.
真是一顿丰盛的晚餐
And what a great dinner.
谢谢
Thank you.
我喜欢下厨
I enjoy cooking.
但愿你不介意我打电话找你
Hope you don't mind my calling you.
有时 独自一人很难熬
Sometimes it's so hard to be alone.
完全不介意
Not at all.
雀茜外出时 我也会有点寂寞
I get a little lonely, too, when Trish is out of town.
你和雀茜结婚多久了
How long have you and Trish been married?
今年九月就是十年了
10 years this September.
十年?
10 years?
太不可思议了
It's really amazing.
从没有人爱我像你爱雀茜那样 没有人
No one has ever loved me the way you love Trish, no one.
你的丈夫呢
What about your husband?
我的丈夫从没爱过我
My husband never loved me.
他都迫不及待地想离开我
He couldn't wait to get away from me.
对不起
I'm sorry.
有时我觉得雀茜也想离开我
Sometimes I think Trish would like to get away from me, too.
可怜的宝贝
Poor baby.
真是个可怜的宝贝
Poor, poor baby.
告诉 什么会让你兴奋
So, tell me, what turns you on?
什么会让我兴奋?
What turns me on?
从没有人问过我 让我想想
Wow, no one's ever asked me that before.Let me think.
你知道什么会让我真的兴奋吗
You know what really turns me on?
飞行
Flying.
飞行?
Flying?
是的 开飞机飞行
Yeah, flying a plane.
你不知道那有多棒
You don't know what kinda high it is.
你在上空飞翔 凌驾一切
You're soarin' up there above everything.
掌握一切
You're in control.
太美妙了
How fantastic.
没错
It really is.
只有那时我对事物的感觉才会真切
It's the only time I feel really clear about things.
有时我会思考人生 好奇我是怎么走到这步的
Sometimes I look at my life and I wonder how I got here.
我感觉我的人生在悄然离去
I feel like my life is slipping away
我却还有很多事没做完
and there's so many things I haven't done.
比如?
Like what?
我从没有过任何外遇
I've never had any sort of love affairs
也没有过任何不端行为
or gotten into any mischief.
我以前常看史蒂夫·麦奎因的老电影
I used to watch those old Steve McQueen movies,
抢银行那种
you know, the ones where they'd rob a bank or something,
我会幻想自己是那些
and I'd fantasize that I was one of those
疯狂歹徒的一员 手里搂着一个性感颓废的姑娘
crazy kinda gangsters with a sexy, messed up girl on my arm.
也会幻想自己是西部片里的人 开枪干服一个镇
Or those westerns, when they'd shoot up a town
然后去搞当地的妓女
and then go visit the local prostitutes.
我知道这听上去很傻
It's sounds stupid, I know.
听上去不傻
No, it doesn't.
很可爱
It's very sweet.
真的吗
Really?
雀茜不这么想
Trish doesn't think so.
我这么说的时候 她就翻白眼
She just rolls her eyes when I talk like this.
那是因为她不理解你
That's because she doesn't understand you.
我完全理解你
I understand you perfectly.
是吗
You do?
当然
Of course.
你想有一次污秽的外遇
You wanna have a sordid love affair.
你想有些不端行为
You wanna get into some mischief.
你是谁
Who are you?
你在对我做什么
What are you doing to me?
我是爱情女巫
I'm the love witch.
我是你的终极幻想
I'm your ultimate fantasy.
就是这样
That's right.
史蒂夫 我要去见那个巫医了
Steve, I'm going out to see that witch doctor.
谁
Who?
金教授
Professor king.
他专攻黑魔法和巫术
He specializes in black magic and witchcraft.
他也许能帮我鉴别一些我们找到的物品
He might be able to help me identify some of the items we found.
那很好
It's great.
你拿到实验室报告了吗
Did you get the lab report?
拿到了 似乎是心脏衰竭
Yeah, yeah, it looks like heart failure.
但毒物学测试报告显示有微量曼陀罗
But the toxicology report showed traces of jimsonweed
也被称为恶魔的大麻 剧毒且致幻
also known as devil's weed, a highly toxic hallucinogenic.
难以置信
It's unbelievable.
你要我和你一起去?
You want me to come with you?
不用 就一会儿时间
No, this will only take a few minutes.
你能帮我点个火鸡肉牛油果全麦面包吗
Can you order me a Turkey and avocado on whole wheat?
加芥末蛋黄酱?
Mustard, Mayo?
是啊 还要凉拌卷心菜
Yeah and Cole slaw.
谢了
Thanks.
好
Done.
金教授
神秘学研究
梅多斯警长 抱歉让你久等了
Sergeant Meadows, sorry to have kept you waiting.
很高兴见到你 教授
Glad to meet you, professor.
教授 这是我们在韦恩·彼得斯的坟里发现的瓶子
Professor, this is the bottle we found in a grave of Wayne Peters,
你在报纸上看到的那个
the one you read about in the paper.
真有趣
Interesting, yes.
正如我所料
Just as I thought.
里面的东西表明这是个女巫瓶
The contents indicate that it's a witch bottle.
女巫瓶?
A witch bottle?
没错 女巫制作它们来防范诅咒
Yes, witches used to make them for protection against curses.
她们会用到自己的体液或头发这种个人的东西
They'd take something personal like bodily fluids or hair
再混上草药
along with herbs
和像是针或碎玻璃的尖锐物来吓走邪灵
and something sharp like pins or broken glass to scare away evil spirits.
女巫瓶经常被发现埋在古老房子的灵车里
Witch bottles have often been found buried in the hearse of very old houses.
可以假设制作这东西的人是个女巫吗
Would it be safe to assume that the person who made this was a witch?
非常有可能
It's very likely.
长眠于文明世界的巫术已再次扎根于城市了
Witchcraft, long dormant in civilized places,has taken root again in cities.
每年都有几次仪式
There have several rituals per year.
其中之一的萨温节 相当于我们的万圣节
One of them, Samhain, corresponds of our Halloween.
其他仪式有庆祝夏至的利萨节
Other rituals celebrate summer solstice, Litha,
有庆祝冬至的伊摩尔格节
or the winter solstice, which they call Imolg.
这是巫师团成员亲吻着魔鬼屁股来嘲弄基督教仪式
Here the members of a coven kiss the devil's behind in a mockery of Christian rituals.
这是一个崇拜撒旦的邪教在献祭一个孩子
Here, a satanic cult sacrifices a child.
如今真有这种事吗
Does this stuff really go on today?
真有
Yes, indeed.
实施人类献祭的是黑巫师
Those who practice human sacrifice are the black witches
他们举行鲜血仪式来获得恶魔般的力量
who perform blood rituals to gain demonic powers
并隐秘地将成员凝聚在一起
and to bind their members together in secrecy.
执法部门几十年来一直想把这些邪教彻底根除
Law has been trying to root out these cults for decades
但一直没成功
but they've been unsuccessful.
还有就是白巫师或威卡信徒
Then there are the white witches or Wiccans
他们通过与大自然沟通来灵疗
who commune in nature in the healing spirit
他们有禁止伤害他人的铁律
and who have a strict law that forbids harming others.
如今的每个城市和农村
Every city and rural village today has pockets
都有一些实施古代仪式的黑巫师和白巫师
of both black and white witches who practice the ancient rites.
我祈求并召唤你 我们所有人的万能之母
I invoke and call upon thee, mighty mother of us all.
我祈求你附身于你的这位仆人和祭司
I invoke thee to descend upon the body of this thy servant and priestess.
阴暗与神圣之母
Of the mother darksome and divine
我以这个动作在此委身于你
here I charge you in this sign.
聆听伟大母亲的话语
Listen to the words of the great mother.
她在古代也被称为阿尔特弥斯
She, who of old, who was also called Artemis,
阿芙罗狄蒂 凯丽德温 戴安娜 爱希丝
Aphrodite, Ceridwyn, Diana, Isis,
还有许多其他的名字
and by many other names.
每当你们需要什么时
Whenever ye have need of anything,
你们要在秘密的地方集合并崇拜我
then ye shall assemble in some secret place and adore me,
我是所有巫师的女王
who am queen of all witches.
你们这些愿意学习所有巫术的人要集合在那
There shall ye assemble, ye who are fain to learn all sorcery.
看啊 所有爱和愉悦的行为都是我的仪式
Behold all acts of love and pleasure are my rituals.
看啊 我从一开始就和你们在一起了
Behold I have been with thee from the beginning
我到达了欲望的尽头
and I am that which is attained at the end of desire.
起来吧
Arise.
亲爱的 今晚你看上去有点心神不定
You're looking a little tense tonight, love.
怎么了
What's the matter?
没什么 不过是我的爱情生活又大起大落了
Oh nothing, just my usual roller coaster love life.
喝一杯放松下
Well, have a drink and relax.
至少对你来说 没什么悲惨的
Nothing's that dire, at least not for you.
对你的受害者来说 就另当别论了
It's an entirely different story for your victims.
什么受害者
What victims?
没必要跟我装清白 亲爱的
There's no need to play miss innocent with me, dearie.
请别碰我
Please, don't touch me.
祝福你 芭芭拉
Bright blessings, Barbara.
很高兴见到你 伊莲
Merry meet, Elaine.
怎么样了
How's it going?
我又没人好约了
I'm back in the dating pool again.
怎么了
What happened?
我还以为你很喜欢你新交往的
I thought you were crazy about that new guy you were seeing,
那个已婚男人
the married man.
没有 我跟他断了
No, I broke it off.
他变得很有心事 闷闷不乐
He just became really obsessive, morose,
他变得很阴沉
and his aura became really murky.
他甚至不想做爱了
He didn't even wanna make love anymore.
他就变得像个女人一样 什么小事都要哭
He became just like a woman, crying at every little thing.
没有男人的样子
There was no polarity.
不过我早该知道会这样
But, I should have known.
他是双鱼座
He's a Pisces.
亲爱的伊莲 你为什么没回我电话 见不到你我会死
理查德
Richard.
我跟你说了我工作时千万别来打扰我
I thought I told you never to interrupt me when I'm working.
你想干嘛
What do you want?
我只是想告诉你我要睡了
I just wanted to let you know that I'm going to bed
还有我在服药
and I'm taking a pill.
你睡吗
Are you coming to bed?
不睡
No.
我还有些工作要做
I have some more work to do.
好吧 那明天见
All right, see you tomorrow, then.
月升草药
魔法药店
我是警局的格里夫·梅多斯警长
Sergeant Griff Meadows of the police department.
我想问你几个问题
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
好的
Okay.
这东西眼熟吗
Does this look familiar to you?
这是个女巫瓶
It's a witch bottle.
你知道是谁制作的吗
Do you have any idea who could have made it?
不知道
No, no I don't.
店里看到过这样的东西吗
Ever seen any of these in here before?
看到过 我们有一些女巫瓶
Yeah, we have some witch bottles.
我给你看一个
I'll show you one.
给
Here's one.
这些瓶子有多常见
How common are these bottles?
在一个姑娘开始把它们供应给我们之前 我就没见过
I've never seen 'em in here before until a girl started supplying 'em to us.
这姑娘是谁
Who is this girl?
她叫伊莲 伊莲·帕克斯
Her name is Elaine, Elaine parks.
谁啊
Who is it?
我是警局的梅多斯警长
Sergeant Meadows, police department.
很抱歉打扰你 夫人 但我在查一件案子
Sorry to bother you, ma'am, but I'm investigating a case
我只是想问你几个问题
and I just wanted to ask you a few questions.
关于什么的
About what?
这可能是一起凶杀案
Well, it's a potential homicide case.
只是例行核查
Just a routine check.
我想你也许能帮到我们
I thought you might be able to help us.
好的
Of course.
请进吧 警长
Please come in, sergeant.
你说有一起凶杀案
So you say there was a homicide.
太可怕了
How horrible.
谁被杀了
Who was killed?
一名叫韦恩·彼得斯的男子
A man named Wayne Peters.
你认识韦恩·彼得斯吗
Did you know Wayne Peters?
不认识
No.
这是他的照片
Here's a picture of him.
以前看到过他吗
Ever seen him before?
没看到过
No.
我想我帮不了你 警长
I guess I can't help you, sergeant.
再见
Good bye.
帕克斯女士 等等
Ms. parks, wait.
你以前见过这样的东西吗
Have you ever seen anything like this before?
这是个魔法瓶
It's a magic bottle.
我自己制作的
I made it myself.
你见过装有尿的吗
Have you ever seen one containing urine?
尿?
Urine?
没见过
No.
我们在韦恩·彼得斯的坟上发现的这个瓶子
We found this bottle containing urine
里面装有尿和一个用过的卫生棉条
and a used tampon on the grave of Wayne Peters.
警长 恕我失陪一会儿
Will you excuse me for a moment, sergeant?
帕克斯女士 你是个女巫吗
Ms. parks, are you a witch?
是的
Yes, I am.
这有违法吗
Is there a law against that?
没有 除非你犯了些事
I guess not, not unless you do something wrong.
你觉得成为女巫就让我变邪恶了?
Do you think that being a witch makes me evil,
甚至能杀人了?
capable of murder even?
没有 我不是想说...
No, I wasn't trying to imply...
梅多斯警长 你知道真正的遭受痛苦是什么滋味吗
Sergeant Meadows, do you know what it's like to really suffer?
你不得不一直抗争 直到你累坏了而无法继续
You have to fight and fight until you're too exhausted to go on.
巫术是我的信仰 警长
Witchcraft is my religion, sergeant.
这种信仰比你的基督教还古老
And this religion, which is older than your Christianity,
它拯救了我的人生
saved my life.
帕克斯女士 有所冒犯的话 我很抱歉
Ms. parks, I'm sorry if I've offended you.
我不是故意的
I didn't realize.
没关系 梅多斯警长
That's all right, sergeant Meadow.
你可以叫我格里夫
You can call me Griff.
格里夫?
Griff?
我知道我以前见过你
I know I've seen you before.
只是不知道是哪见到的
I just don't know where.
我有同样的感觉
I have that same feeling.
我知道了
I know.
你是牌里的那个人
You're the man in the cards.
你是我的命运
You're my fate.
什么叫我是你的命运
What do you mean, I'm your fate?
我做过一次凯尔特十字解读
I did a Celtic cross reading.
我的未来牌是权杖骑士
For my future card I got knight of wands.
一直觉得那张牌在做未来解读时出现的话
Always felt that if that card showed up in a future reading,
我就会很快遇见我要嫁的男人
soon meet the man that I'm going to marry.
但我要嫁的男人得喜欢动物
But, the man that I marry has to love animals.
你喜欢动物吗 格里夫
Do you like animals, Griff?
喜欢啊 我喜欢动物
Why yes, I love animals.
事实上 我的一个朋友有几匹马
In fact, a friend of mine has a couple horses
我非常喜欢
I'm very fond of.
明天我休息
You know, tomorrow is my day off
外出应该很不错
and it's supposed to be quite nice out.
或许我要去远离城市的地方骑马
Maybe I'll get away from the city and do some riding.
你喜欢骑马吗 伊莲
Do you like to ride, Elaine?
广藿香 你真是个甜心
Oh patchouli, you're such a sweetheart.
我的女孩还好吗
How's my girl?
我是你的女孩?
Am I your girl?
今天是的
For today you are.
你是我的女孩 否则周围也没人能告诉我了
You're my girl and there's nobody around to tell me otherwise.
除了我
Except me.
那是什么意思
And what's that supposed to mean?
没什么意思
Nothing.
那是什么声音
What's that sound?
不知道
I don't know.
我们去看看
Let's go see.
现在是夏至了
Now is the time of the summer solstice.
橡树王的力量在减弱
The strength of the oak king is waning.
冬青树王为了绿色少女
And the Holly king stands ready to challenge him
已做好了向他挑战的准备
for the hand of the green maiden.
战斗开始
Let the battle begin.
你的季节结束了 老头
Your season is over old man.
绝对不会
Oh never.
我会拥有她
I will have her.
绝不会拥有她
Never have her.
绝不会
Never.
冬青树王 我宣布你是胜利者
Holly king, I name you the Victor.
绿色少女是你的了
The green maiden is yours.
我的女士
My lady
来吧
Come on.
伊莲
Elaine.
你认识这些人?
You know these people?
某方面来说 是的
Well yes, in a way.
你们好 我们是公平领主和夫人
All hail, fair lord and lady.
欢迎来到我们的小聚会
Welcome to our little gathering.
你们好
All hail.
我们是文艺复兴时期的仙人
We are the good people of the renaissance
和中世纪演员 我们正在庆祝仲夏
and medieval players and we are celebrating the midsummer.
不想加入我们吗
Won't you join us?
当然想 公平领主
To be sure, fair consort.
他们很迷人 对吗
They are charming, are they not?
是的 相当迷人
Yes, quite charming.
我看到了两个相爱的人
I see two people in love.
这意味着一场婚礼
This calls for a wedding.
一场婚礼?
A wedding?
是的 一场模拟婚礼 如果你愿意的话
Yes, a mock wedding, if you will.
以此向爱神表达敬意
To honor the gods of love.
好吧
Okay.
现在你们已结为夫妻
Now, ye are wed.
我很为你高兴 伊莲 他很可爱
I'm so happy for you, Elaine, he's adorable.
我没恋爱
I'm not in love.
不是说我没感情
It's not that I don't have sentiment,
只是爱情是柔弱的
it's just that love is soft.
在我这一行 你需要胆量
You need guts in this business.
我见过被开枪致死的男人 因为他们恋爱了
I've seen guys get shot to death because they fell in love
内心变得柔弱了
and got soft inside.
我希望将来有继承人
I want an heir some day
我会需要一个妻子
and then I would need to have a wife,
但爱情是另外一回事
but love is something else.
一个男人会被这样的东西摧毁
A man can get destroyed by things like that.
就好像他不会再是一个男人了
It's like he's not even a man anymore.
我绝不想变成那样
I never wanna get that way.
你真的爱他时
When you really love him,
那感觉就像烟花 而别的事都无关紧要了
it's like fireworks and nothing else matters.
你喜欢他的所有小怪癖
You love all the little quirks about him.
喜欢他吃麦片的方式
The way he slurps his cereal.
喜欢他嘴巴略歪的样子
The way his mouth is a little crooked.
他身上的那些细节变成了你的一辈子
Those details about him become your whole life.
你的内心就如花朵一样绽开了
Something inside you opens up like a flower
你会发现你还能给予更多的爱
and you realize that you have more love to give
你以前从未觉得这是可能的事
than you ever thought was possible.
因为你越了解他
'Cause the more you know him,
你就越爱他
the more you love him.
你越了解一个女人
The more you get to know a woman,
你对她的感觉就越少
the less you can feel about her.
起初 她是个不可思议的神秘对象
At first, she's this incredible object of mystery
能满足你所有的狂野幻想
who fulfills all you're wildest fantasies.
接着 她会开始显露小缺点
Then she starts to reveal little flaws
一段时间之后 她就变得非常难照顾
and after a while, just gets pretty hard to care.
理想女性只存在于男人的脑海中
Feminine ideal only exists in a man's mind.
没有女人能做到
No woman could ever fulfill it.
有时 她想更爱你
And sometimes, when she tries to love you more,
给予你更多 你会感觉自己快窒息了
give you more, you feel like you're suffocating,
快淹死在雌激素中
drowning in estrogen.
这是最可怕的感觉
The most awful feeling.
今晚一起吃晚餐吗 格里夫
Dinner tonight, Griff?
今晚没空 康妮
Um, can't tonight, Connie.
改天吧
Some other time.
嘿 格里夫 那个姑娘 伊莲·帕克斯 我有她更多的信息了
Hey Griff, I got more information on that Elaine parks girl.
丢我办公桌上吧
You leave it on my desk.
你不想听吗
Don't you wanna hear it?
史蒂夫 警监要我们撤销这案子
Steve, captain wants us to lay off the case.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
他说我们有不烦扰巫师的政策
He says we have a policy of leaving the witches alone.
他说他们在这镇上生活很久了 他不喜欢惹他们
He says they've lived in this town a long time and he doesn't like to mess with them.
就算杀人也不管?
Even if they murder?
他说他确信韦恩死于心脏病
He says he's satisfied that Wayne's death was a heart attack.
我也这么认为
I think so too.
这里每个人都疯了吗
Has everyone gone crazy around here?
至少让我告诉你我发现了什么
Let me at least tell you what I found.
伊莲和她丈夫杰瑞以前在伯克利经营一家有机美容店
Now, Elaine used to run an organic beauty store in Berkeley with her husband, Jerry.
两年后 他们离婚了
Two years later they were divorced
伊莲搬到了旧金山 开始在滑稽表演俱乐部跳舞
and Elaine moved to San Francisco to start dancing at a burlesque club
她就在那里涉足了一个巫师团
where she got involved with a witch coven.
此团有些人离奇死亡 在警方盘问死亡时间后就解散了
The coven broke up after police questioning when some of it's members died mysteriously.
没多久 伊莲的前夫死于药物过量
Soon after, Elaine's exhusband died of a drug overdose
而前不久 他正打算再婚
shortly before he was planning to remarry.
警方盘问了伊莲
The police questioned Elaine
但他们没足够证据抓她
but they couldn't find enough to hold her.
如果旧金山警方什么都找不到
Well, if the San Francisco police couldn't find anything,
那我们要管了干嘛
what happened there is none of our business.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
我想说这女人是个危险人物
I'd say this woman is a dangerous character
你最好注意好她
and you better watch her.
就因为她是个女巫?
You mean because she's a witch?
这什么都说明不了
That doesn't mean anything.
她丈夫死于他以前从没服用过的药物
No, her husband died of a drug he'd never taken before.
韦恩·彼得斯从哪弄到恶魔的大麻的 你知道吗
And did you ever find where Wayne Peters got the devil's weed?
这我问过柯蒂斯女士
I questioned Ms. Curtis about that.
他小屋旁 长有恶魔的大麻
There was devil's weed growing near his cabin.
很显然 他经常试验毒品
Apparently, he experimented often with drugs.
拜托 格里夫 你不能把关键点联系起来吗
Come on Griff, can't you connect the dots?
我们这有一起可能的谋杀案
We have a possible murder here
而伊莲是我们唯一的嫌疑人
and Elaine is our only suspect.
我跟你说过我们撤案了
I told you, we're laying off her.
是因为命令 还是因为你爱上她了
Because of orders or because you're in love with her?
谁说我爱上她了
Who says I'm in love with her?
别来烦我了
Get the hell off my back.
你过分了 格里夫 太过分了
You're out of line, Griff, way out of line.
理查德
Richard.
Richard!
理查德
谢谢你来见我 伊莲
Thank you for meeting me, Elaine.
太孤单的感觉对我来说并不好
It's not good for me to be alone too much.
我知道你很忙
I know you're busy.
当然
Of course.
我一直想来
I wanted to come.
我忍不住为所发生的事而自责
I can't help but blaming myself for what happened.
你不能怪自己
You can't blame yourself.
对理查德而言 你是个好妻子
You were a good wife to Richard.
我也想
I tried to be.
我很努力地去取悦他了
I tried so hard to please him,
但我本该更努力的
but I should have tried harder.
他想要的那种女人 我永远成不了
He wanted a certain type of woman, someone I could never be.
也许你是对的
Maybe you were right.
也许你应该满足一个男人的幻想
Maybe you should give a man his fantasy.
你这么说时 我觉得这很差劲
I thought that was so awful when you said that.
也许我一直都太天真
Maybe I was being naive,
原本我真认为他因为我这个人而爱我
but I really thought he loved me for me.
可现在 我希望...
But now, now I wish...
你不能再折磨自己了
You have to stop torturing yourself.
你得放手
You have to let go.
我去了次达拉斯 回来后他都变什么样了
Remember how he changed after my Dallas trip?
我想他就是在那期间开始有外遇的
I think that's when he started having that affair.
不管她是谁 她让他痴狂了
Whoever she was she drove him crazy.
对此 我恨死他了
I hated him so much for that.
我想杀了他们两个
I wanted to kill them both.
我要是发现她是谁了 我会把她撕成碎片
If I ever found out who she was, I would rip her to pieces.
但现在我才明白我原本应该帮助他的
But now I see I should have helped him.
我不知道他会自寻短见
I didn't know that he was going to take his own life.
嘿
Hey,
hey.
不说我了
Enough about me.
你怎么样
What's going on with you?
雀茜 我恋爱了
Trish, I'm in love.
他是谁
Who is he?
他是个警探 他是一个女人想要的一切
He's a detective and he's everything a woman could ever want.
他强壮英俊 聪明善良
He's strong and handsome, smart and kind.
我知道他就是那个人
I just know that he's the one.
他还给了我这个戒指
He even gave me this ring.
我管它叫我的魔法戒指
I call it my magic ring.
这不是订婚戒指 但我知道他很快就会求婚了
It's not an engagement ring, but I just know that he's gonna pop the question soon.
我们第一次来这时 我给你看了我的订婚戒指 记得吗
When we first came here I showed you my engagement ring, remember?
我几乎没法再看着它了 太痛苦了
I can barely stand to look at it anymore.It's too painful.
我肯定他很快会向你求婚的
I'm sure he's going to ask you soon.
你会是一个美丽的新娘
You're going to make a beautiful bride.
我们相见的第一天
The first day we met,
你羡慕我 因为我有男人
you were envious of me because I had a man
而你是单身
and you were all alone.
现在反过来了
Now it's the reverse.
生活真是有趣 对吧
Life is funny, isn't it?
雀茜 抱歉 我得走了
Trish, I'm sorry, I've gotta go.
你想和我一起出去吗
Would you like to walk out with me?
不了 我想待着把茶喝完
No, I'd like to stay and finish my tea.
好的
All right.
保重 亲爱的
Take care, love.
嗨 伊莲 是我
Hi Elaine, it's me.
你把戒指落下了
Yeah, you left your ring here.
你大概上路了 不过我回家时会顺路送来
You're probably driving but I'll drop it by on my way home.
一会儿见
See you in a minute.
理查德
用于理查德的爱情法术
生日快乐
献给世界上最美的女士 她生日了 今晚见 爱你的 理查德
你个婊子
You bitch.
你害死了我丈夫
You killed my husband.
婊子 荡妇 妓女
Bitch, skank, whore.
你会为此而被烧死
You'll burn for this.
撞车 撞车 撞车
Crash, crash, crash.
死吧 死吧 死吧
Die, die, die.
哈邦蒂雅啊 用一杯让人沉醉的爱侣佳酿
Oh Habondia, bind these two
将此二人结合吧
with a heady lovers' brew.
即便他们奋力逃离
Even should they strive to flee
还是会永远相依
they'll cling for all eternity.
苏格兰威士忌
Scotch.
一瓶啤酒 山姆
Bottle o' beer, Sam.
这两个新来的姑娘是谁
Who are those new girls?
她们根本不会跳舞
They can't dance at all.
而且她们很怪异
And they're weird.
不知道 但客人很喜欢她们
I don't know, but the customers really like 'em.
她们是巫师的朋友
They're friends of the witches.
我以前看到他们一起进来的
I seen them come in together before.
没错 巫师
Yeah, the witches.
他们无处不在
They're everywhere.
一杯加奎宁水的杜松子酒 山姆
One gin and tonic, Sam.
加奎宁水的杜松子酒 马上来
Gin and tonic coming up.
你们看了那个被埋在自己小屋后院的教师的报道没
Did you read about the teacher buried in the back yard of his cabin?
据说是巫师挖的
They said it was dug by the witches.
我看了 他们在坟上发现了各种巫术制品
Oh yeah, I read about that.They found all kinds of witchcraft things on the grave.
没错 我也听说了
Yeah, I heard about that, too.
瘆人
Creepy.
坐下 伊莲
Sit down, Elaine.
伊莲 从实验室拿回的DNA
Elaine, the DNA came back from the lab.
表明你和韦恩·彼得斯有关联
It connects you with Wayne Peters.
帕雀茜亚·曼宁来了次警局
Patricia Manning came by the station.
带了些你的东西来
Some things of yours.
包括这个
Including this.
她说你害得她丈夫自杀了
She said you drove her husband to suicide.
所以 我是个坏女孩
So, I was a bad girl.
你要惩罚我吗
Are you going to punish me?
你是什么样的人 伊莲
What sort of person are you, Elaine?
什么样的病态思维会做这种事
What sort of sick mind would do such things?
你怎么这么消极
Why are you so negative?
我谁也没杀啊
I didn't kill anyone.
韦恩在春宵一夜后
Wayne died of heart failure
死于心脏衰竭
after a beautiful night of lovemaking.
理查德死于他太爱我了
And Richard died because he loved me too much.
这些男人不习惯与我在一起时的深情之爱
These men weren't used to the deep feelings of love that they were experiencing with me.
你是说这些男人死于爱情?
Are you saying these men died of love?
你疯了吧
That's insane.
法术和毒药怎么说呢
What about the spells and the drugs?
你想说巫术与此毫无关系吗
Are you saying witchcraft had nothing to do with it?
巫术只是集中能量的一种方式
Witchcraft is just a way of concentrating energy.
它只对已经存在的有效
It can only work with what's already there.
我只是用性爱魔法来创造爱情魔法
I just use sex magic to create love magic.
我不知道法术会有多强大
I didn't know how strong the spells would be.
有时得到的爱情强烈得差点吓到我
Sometimes it's almost scary how strong the love gets.
爱情?
Love?
你知道什么是爱情吗
What do you know about love?
你所谓的爱情是一种边缘型人格障碍
What you call love is a borderline personality disorder
或者更糟
or worse.
别给我做诊断
Don't diagnose me.
也许你是个没法爱的自恋狂
Maybe you're a narcissist who can't love.
你觉得我病了
You think that I'm sick
因为你从没像我一样爱过
because you've never loved like I have.
我会为爱做任何事
Well, I would do anything for love.
没错 你永远都得不到足够的爱
That's right, you'll never get enough love.
即使一个男人爱你爱得无法自拔而自杀
Even when a man loves you so much it kills him,
对你来说还是不够
it's not enough for you.
你就像一个无底洞
You're like a bottomless hole.
你把自己打扮得花枝招展 做斯戴佛式妻子做的事
You doll yourself up and do the Stepford wife thing
以为每个男人都会拜倒在你的石榴裙下
thinking every man is going to fall at your feet.
但你那瘆人的性感小把戏对我不起作用
But your creepy little sexy act doesn't work with me.
我不爱你
I don't love you.
你怎么能在那吹嘘自己免疫爱情呢
How can you stand there and boast about being immune to love?
为什么一个女人真挚的爱会让你如此害怕
Why does the genuine love of a woman scare you so much?
你觉得你这样活着很优越吗
You think that your way is a superior way to live?
我认识很多和我有一样看法的女人
I know a lot of women who feel the way that I do.
只有男人会让我们为了你们的爱而非常努力地工作
Only men make us work so hard for your love.
只要你们是因为我们这个人而爱我们
If you would just love us for ourselves,
但你不会
but you won't.
我的前夫就像你一样
My exhusband was just like you.
他对我抑制他的爱 以此来惩罚我
He used to punish me by withholding his love from me.
我这辈子一直在被扔进垃圾堆
All my life I've been tossed in the garbage
除了男人想用我身体的时候
except when men wanted to use my body.
所以我决定要找到自己的力量
So, I decided to find my own power.
我通过巫术发现了我的力量
And I found that power through witchcraft.
这意味着我能从男人那里拿取我所需要的
That means that I take what I need from men
而不是反过来
and not the other way around.
对不起 伊莲
I'm sorry, Elaine.
这次不会有效果了
It won't work this time.
我恐怕我得逮捕你
I'm afraid I'm going to have to arrest you.
因为什么呢
What for?
根据我的信仰来嫁给情人?
Marrying a lover according to my religion?
勾引有妇之夫?
Seducing a married man?
我知道400年前你会因为这种事而被烧死
I know 400 years ago you could be burned for a thing like that,
但如今不会了
but not today.
没错 不会被烧死了
No, not burned,
但你会因非法埋葬韦恩·彼得斯而被抓
but you'll be booked for burying Wayne Peters illegally
我们还会进一步调查
and we'll find out more.
就是这个女巫杀了那教师
That's the witch who killed the teacher.
你不用为遭受一个女巫而活
Thou shalt not suffer a witch to live.
烧死女巫
Burn the witch.
烧死女巫 烧死女巫 烧死女巫...
Burn the witch, burn the witch, burn the witch...
烧死女巫 烧死女巫 烧死女巫
burn the witch, burn the witch, burn the witch.
烧死她
Burn her.
Burn.
可怜的宝贝
Poor baby.
真是个可怜的宝贝
Poor, poor baby.
别担心 一切都会好的
Don't worry, everything will be okay
因为我好爱你
because I love you so much.
我爱你 伊莲
I love you, Elaine.
除了你 我从没爱过任何人
I've never loved anyone but you.
我想和你结婚
I want to marry you.
译者：微博@Emtee